electronichouse.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy policy - Electronic House

**EH PUBLISHING, Inc. DBA EH MEDIA PRIVACY POLICY**

Latest Update May 25, 2018

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, stored, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from EH Media’s Network of Web Sites (this “site” Including campussafetymagazine.com, cepro.com, commercialintegrator.com, electronichouse.com, mytechdecisions.com, prosoundweb.com, roboticsbusinessreview.com, robobusiness.com, campussafetyconference.com, campussafetyhq.com, channelpronetwork.com, and iotplaybook.com

**YOUR INFORMATION: WHAT DATA WE COLLECT AND HOW WE COLLECT IT**

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your device, web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For example, we utilize cookies to limit the frequency in which you may see a particular advertisement, or to prevent submitting a response to a survey or quiz if you had already completed it. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, pages consumed, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. In addition, we use a 3rd party- Google Analytics to collect, monitor and analyze this data so that we can better understand how visitors use our web sites. This data is also anonymized and cannot be traced back to an individual user. 

– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record anonymous information about how you browse the Site. For more information about this technology and how it is used please visit the online advertising glossary at: [https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/glossary/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/glossary/)

Many of our sites require you to provide certain information about yourself when you register to use the site and when you request access to downloadable resources, our products and/or services. We also collect information when you participate in contests and surveys, when you respond to requests for feedback and when you submit postings to public areas of this Site (e.g., comments, blogs, moderated discussions and forums/message boards). The information we collect may include information from which you may be personally identified (“Personally Identifiable Information”), such as name, postal address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address, and certain business information such as employer name, occupation, job function, job title and buying information (e.g., preferences or history). This Site only collects Personally Identifiable Information with your knowledge. This applies to information collected on our sites directly, and information collected at branded landing pages (not necessarily owned and operated by EH Media).

Some of the materials included on this Site, including advertising, may be served by third parties. These third parties, in the course of serving such materials, may collect information regarding your use of this Site and how you respond to e-mail communications, using methods that may include automatic data collection, and may use this information in order to present advertisements or other content that may be of interest to you on both this Site and on other web sites. Collection, use, disclosure and security of information collected by third parties are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties. If you would like more information about this practice or to opt out of having this information used by certain third-party ad servers to provide targeted ads, please visit: http://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy#choices. 

You also may view the privacy policy of AppNexus, Open Ad Stream, a third-party that serves ads to our web sites, at [https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy](https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy).

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, credit card payment information, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

We use the Device Information generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the effectiveness of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

We also use Device Information such as cookies, beacons, tags and pixels to extend relevant advertising opportunities to other 3rd party web sites you may visit such as Facebook. Please see the BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING section below for more information. 

We may also use Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address).

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site. This includes processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with order confirmations, invoices, and cancellation notices. Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

Communicate with you;

Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and

When in line with the permissions you have granted us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use any Personally Identifiable Information collected on this Site for the following purposes:

To provide you with this Site and other products and services; and

To respond to your inquiries and contact you about changes regarding the Site

To provide you with e-mail, fax and other notices (such as expiration and renewal notices) regarding your account and the products or services that you are receiving, and for billing and collection purposes if applicable.

For any other purpose disclosed at the time the information is collected or to which you consent.

**SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We share your site Device Information with third parties to help us use that information, as described above. This data is aggregated and anonymized. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). 

When you have shared Personally Identifiable Information with us to access a premium resource or download we may share that Personally Identifiable Information with a 3rd party sponsor or sponsor(s) for their own marketing purposes. Whenever we intend to share your Personally Identifiable Information with a 3rd party we will clearly indicate that your data will be shared at the time when you provide us with your information. We never share Personally Identifiable Information with any 3rd party without your knowledge. Any 3rd parties who acquire your Personally Identifiable Information from EH Media must provide you with access to their own published Privacy Policies.

We may also share your Personally Identifiable Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

Finally, we may also share your Personally Identifiable Information to any successor pursuant to an asset sale, merger, consolidation, restructuring, reorganization, liquidation or other similar transaction involving EH Publishing, Inc. D.B.A EH Media or this Site

**BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:

APP NEXUS (Our Ad Serving Technology) – [http://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy#choices](http://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy#choices)

FACEBOOK – [https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads)

ADDAPTIVE (Our Ad Retargeting Technology) – [https://www.addaptive.com/privacy/](https://www.addaptive.com/privacy/)

GOOGLE – [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous)

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/)

**DO NOT TRACK**

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser, unless you are visiting from a European country.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

All Visitors

To add, change, or remove any email communication preferences you may have set with us you may simply use the “Manage Preferences” link found at the bottom of all of our commercial email communications with you. 

European Visitors under General Data Protection Regulation

If you are visiting the site from Europe, our site will use geo-location to determine your relative country of origin. Upon first visit European users will be presented with a dialog box that describes the types of cookies the site is using and will ask for explicit consent to accept cookies in use for Personalization, Statistics and Marketing cookies. This consent is stored for 12 months, at which time the dialog will be presented to the user again to provide explicit consent for another 12 months. Acceptance of each cookie type is not required; however some site functions may be limited or not function as intended if the cookie is not accepted and cannot be placed in the users browser. Browser based “Do Not Track” requests are automatically accepted by our system for European site visitors. Click here to renew or change your cookie consent _Note: Cookie Declaration Link Will Only Function for European Visitors_

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right and request an audit or deletion of your data, please contact us via email at [cpo@ehpub.com](mailto:cpo@ehpub.com). Please allow up to 3 business days (72 hours) for a response from us. 

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your transactional information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

**DATA RETENTION**

Cookies: Our site uses both Persistent and Session based Cookies.

A Persistent Cookie is one that will stay in your browser until it expires or you clear your browsers cookie file. An example of a Persistent Cookie is one that remembers your information when you filled out a form to access a download, so the next time you complete one of our forms you do not have to fill out any fields except any new responses necessary. In this case, this cookie expires annually.

A Session Cookie is one that is only in use until you end your session (leave the site). An example of a Session Cookie is our advertising cookie which will only allow you to see only one (1) of our interstitial ads during your session. If you visit the site again- starting a new session, the cookie is reset and you may see one (1) of those ads again. 

_Note: Some site functions may be limited or not function as intended if the users browser is configured to not accept cookies._

Personally Identifiable Data: Any Personally Identifiable Data that you have provided is stored in our databases for three years as long as you are still engaging with our sites and brands, and is appended as you continue to interact with our site and modify your preferences.

Transactional Data: When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

Please see our [Data Protection Policy](https://mytechdecisions.com/eh-media-data-protection-policy/) for further information.

**MINORS**

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 16.

**CHANGES**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

**CONTACT US**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to submit a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at [cpo@ehpub.com](mailto:cpo@ehpub.com) or by mail using the details provided below.

**WEB SITE OWNED AND OPERATED BY:**

EH Publishing, Inc. DBA EH Media, 111 SPEEN ST., FRAMINGHAM, MA, 01701, United States

This Site contains content, services, advertising and other materials that link to Web sites operated by third parties. We have no control over those other sites, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them. We encourage you to refer to the privacy policies, if any, of those sites.
